http://www.autoliv.com/site-services/privacy-policy

Data Privacy Notice for COVID-19 data processing
This Privacy Policy describes how we handle data for our services on this Autoliv Inc. website (“autoliv.com”), which kind of data we collect, store, and process during your use of the publicly accessible parts of the website, for which purpose we collect, store, and process the data, and how we use the data.
Collection and processing of personal data
You can generally browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any other personal information about yourself. For system-related and statistical purposes, including providing a better service in the future, we will however automatically record every access to the website and every download of a file stored on the website. The log server protocol will include the name of the accessed file, time and date of the access, the volume of data transmitted, confirmation of successful download, web browser, operating system, the referring domain, and the IP address of the enquiring computer. This also includes the purpose of maintaining a sustainable and reliable level of IT-security in your and Autoliv’s interest, as we detect possible intrusion attempts and have measures in place that ensure your and Autoliv’s security.
In addition, we record the personal data (such as name, address and e-mail address) such that you enter in forms on the website and process it for sending requested material and/or information about us as well as for the respective purposes indicated in connection with the form on the website. The logged data and personal data will not be merged with data from other sources and will not be passed on to third parties outside the Autoliv Group (“Third Parties”), and the IP address will only be stored as long as necessary and will not be passed on to Third Parties.
Use of cookies
A „cookie“ is a small string of information that the website saves temporarily on your computer when you visit the website. Cookies help us in creating more comfortable and efficient offers on the website, including routing user traffic correctly and facilitating excel workbook navigation. Cookies pose no risk to your computer, as they are simply text files and not executable programs. We use various cookies that enable us to provide you the services and information that you are looking for. You can disable cookies in your internet browser options at any time and delete existing cookies. You will find further details in the online help of your browser. However, not all functionalities of the website are accessible without cookies. Your browser may already be set to display a warning whenever it receives a cookie. This warning can be very disruptive. We therefore recommend that you set your browser to always accept cookies from www.autoliv.com. You can change this setting for individual websites. You can find more information on the use of cookies and on how to deactivate cookies at www.meine-cookies.org or www.youronlinechoices.com
Some of the cookies we use are required to provide our website. Other cookies are used to better understand our visitors, to improve our website and services and to deliver advertisements more relevant to you and your interests. We introduce our use of cookies in the following sections.
We use so-called “session cookies” that will be stored only for the duration of your use of the website until you log off. They are part of our ADAM system used to maintain a persistent connection to the website. Load balancer cookies are implemented to keep track on what balanced node you are on, and we also use cookies to provide you with excel workbook navigation. In addition to this, we also use other categories of cookies: Essential Cookies, Functionality Cookies, Performance Cookies and Targeting and Advertising Cookies.This categorization mainly corresponds to that of the International Chamber of Commerce (ICC), UK Cookie guide published in April 2012, which may be accessed at the link below and which contains a description of these cookies).www.international-chamber.co.uk/components/com_wordpress/wp/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/icc_uk_cookie_guide.pdf
Please find below a detailed overview on which cookies we have implemented on this website to provide the required sophisticated services.
Name
Description
Provider
Category
Duration
__cfduid
This cookie is set by the CloudFlare service to identify trusted web traffic. It does not correspond to any user id in the web application, nor does the cookie store any personally identifiable information.
CloudFlare
Security
30 days
_ga
Tracking if you've visited before and used to manage the rate at which page view requests are made
Google Analytics
Optional
2 years
_gid
Tracking if you've visited before and used to manage the rate at which page view requests are made
Google Analytics
Optional
24 hours
_gat
This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics, according to documentation it is used to throttle the request rate - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites. It expires after 10 minutes.
Google Analytics
Optional
1 minute
_gac_
Contains campaign related information for the user. If you have linked your Google Analytics and Google Ads accounts, Google Ads website conversion tags will read this cookie unless you opt-out.
Google Analytics
Optional
90 days
__utma
Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Google Analytics
Optional
2 years
__utmt
Used to throttle request rate.
Google Analytics
Optional
10 minutes
__utmb
Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Google Analytics
Optional
30 minutes
__utmc
Not used in ga.js. Set for interoperability with urchin.js. Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the __utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit.
Google Analytics
Optional
End of browser session
__utmz
Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Google Analytics
Optional
6 months
__utmv
Used to store visitor-level custom variable data. This cookie is created when a developer uses the _setCustomVar method with a visitor level custom variable. This cookie was also used for the deprecated _setVar method. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Google Analytics
Optional
2 years
nmstat
This cookie is used to help record visitors' use of the website.It is used to collect statistics about site usage such as when the visitor last visited the site. This information is then used to improve the user experience on the website.
Siteimprove
Optional
3 years
_fbp
Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real-time bidding from third party advertisers.
Facebook
Strictly necessary
90 days
1P_JAR
These cookies are used by Google to display personalized advertisements on Google sites, based on recent searches and previous interactions.
Google
Strictly necessary
30 days
AWSALBCORS
This cookie is managed by AWS and is used for load balancing.
Amazon Web Services
Strictly necessary
7 days
AWSALB
These cookies allows them to deliver their service seamlessly from multiple services using a load balancer, so the cookie simply records which server cluster is serving you.
Amazon Web Services
Strictly necessary
7 days
__CookieConsentV200
For remembering if user has given consent to allow cookies
Autoliv
Strictly necessary
7 days
has_js
This cookie is used to indicate whether or not the visitors browser has JavaScript enabled.
JavaScript
Strictly necessary
Session
AWSELB
These cookies allows them to deliver their service seamlessly from multiple services using a load balancer, so the cookie simply records which server cluster is serving you.
Amazon Web Services
Strictly necessary
7 days
AWSALBTG
AWS Application Load Balancer Cookie. Load Balancing Cookie: Used to encode information about the selected target group.
Amazon Web Services
Strictly necessary
7 days
AWSALBTGCORS
AWS Application Load Balancer Cookie. Load Balancing Cookie: It includes the same information as the original stickiness cookie plus this SameSite attribute.
Amazon Web Services
Strictly necessary
7 days
We also use cookies from Google, Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”) to enable the use of JavaScript and office location maps, and cookies of Cision AB, Linnégatan 87A, PO Box 24194, SE-104 51 Stockholm, Sweden (“Cision”) in order to operate the news feed. This enables Google in the US and Cision in Sweden and its subsidiaries to receive information about you having accessed the respective part of this website. Please check: http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/ and http://news.cision.com/global/_editorial/privacyStatement for more information on the scope of Google’s and Cision’s data collection and data processing and on your respective rights. Please note that we accept no liability for the content of Google’s and Cision’s privacy policy.
Use of AddThis
This website uses social plugins (“Plugins”) provided by addthis.com, operated by AddThis, LLC, 1595 Spring Hill Rd, Suite 300, Vienna, VA 22182, USA (“AddThis”). The Plugins bear a Facebook (white letter “f” on blue background), Twitter (white letter “t” on blue background), and LinkedIn (white letters “in” on blue background) logo. Your browser establishes a direct connection to AddThis servers once you visit a page of our website that contains a Plugin. AddThis then directly transfers the Plugin content to your browser which embeds it into the website. This enables AddThis to receive information about you having accessed the respective part of this website. The Plugin provides AddThis with information about your access of the page of the website on which the Plugin is embedded, including information on the time of use and browser language. Every time you interact with the Plugin by clicking on it, the information is transmitted from your browser directly to AddThis in the USA and stored by AddThis. This may even apply if you are not logged on the Facebook, LinkedIn, or Twitter. Autoliv will not use the information transmitted to AddThis for own purposes.Please check http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy for more information on the scope of AddThis’ data collection and data processing and on your respective rights. Please note that we accept no liability for the content of AddThis’ privacy policy. You can object to the use of your data by AddThis by placing an “opt-out-cookie” on your computer as described on http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out.
Transfer of your personal data
We generally do not transfer your personal data to Third Parties. We only save it and transfer it if it is necessary for completing contractual obligations or after you have expressly consented to the transfer.
Your Data Subject Rights
Based on European Data Protection Regulation and other relevant Data Protection Laws you are entitled to address inquiries regarding your data subject rights towards Autoliv concerning the application that collect and process your personal data. These rights include the ‘Right to be Forgotten’ and the ‘Right to be Informed’. Please address your inquiries regarding this to Autoliv’s Data Protection Office. You can find the address details below. To remove the cookies stored on your computer, please do so in your browser settings. Further instructions for your specific browser can be found in the instructions provided by the supplier.
Privacy policy changes
We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review. This Privacy Policy was last changed on April 23, 2018. If we make changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be announced on this website. Please be sure to check this page before proceeding to use this website.
Contact
If you have any questions on the processing of your personal data, please contact Autoliv’s Data Protection Office: ALV-DataPrivacy@autoliv.com. Please consider that any email that is not related to data protection inquiries will be deleted without sending a reply to it.
